<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title> on Mixed thoughts on Software </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://eliaslindholm.github.io/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design by Contract supported by tests</title>
      <link>http://eliaslindholm.github.io/post/2016/contract-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eliaslindholm.github.io/post/2016/contract-test/</guid>
      <description>In this post I’m going to describe a testing technique that I often find superior to mocking and stubbing. Contract test&amp;rsquo;s and lightweight implementations applies to all level of testing, but in this post im going to describe it in the context of unit testing where i personally use it a lot to define and verify the behavior of an API. The concept of a Contract Test is not new. I first read a about it in the &amp;ldquo;JUnit recipies&amp;rdquo; book sometime during the last decade, although the author didn’t define them as Contract Tests back then, but rather a teqnique for testing abstract types (abstract classes and interfaces in Java).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://eliaslindholm.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eliaslindholm.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer working in the financial industry in Stockholm, Sweden. I&amp;rsquo;m a big proponent of test driven development, although i try to avoid being dogmatic. I don&amp;rsquo;t think there’s one true way to develop software. Different styles suit different needs. Whether a given practice is appealing is highly subjective. For me, TDD really helps me in many of my everyday programming tasks. I will probably write a fair amount of posts about how I do TDD.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

